partstree.com 2018-07-20

# Lawn Mower Parts, Small Engine Parts & Much More! | PartsTree.com - Briggs, MTD, Toro, Cub Cadet, Husqvarna, Troy-bilt...

## Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

## Information Collected

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the PartsTree.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

> Name  
>  Address  
>  Email address  
>  Phone number  
>  Credit/Debit Card Information  
> 

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you make an order and want to send it to a different billing address, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of information collected are:

> Name  
>  Address  
> 

## The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order.

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

After placing an order on this site, you may receive the opportunity to provide feedback on your experience to ShopperApproved.com, an independent customer review service. If you are selected for this opportunity, we will use the email address provided during the ordering process to send this one-time invitation. The survey is entirely voluntary and has no impact on your order. If you choose to complete the survey, any feedback information collected by ShopperApproved.com is governed by their privacy policy which is available at <http://www.shopperapproved.com/privacypolicy.php>.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

## Our Commitment to Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## How You Can Access or Correct Your Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by PartsTree.com. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

## How to Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 512-288-4355.
